Guide to the William D. Wittliff Papers
The Wittliff Collections
William D. Wittliff Papers
1968-1995
The Wittliff Collections
William D. Wittliff
SWWC.026
498 Linear Feet
517 boxes
The Bill Wittliff papers document the book publishing, photography, and screenwriting and filmmaking aspects of Mr. Wittliff's various professional and personal pursuits, ranging in date from 1968-1995, and including the following formats: correspondence, typescript drafts, bibliographies, woodcut blocks, illustrations, photographs, screenplay drafts, film storyboards and other production materials. See series descriptions within the container list for more detailed information.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must secure permission from the Wittliff estate for reproduction of photographs or screenplays
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gifts of Bill and Sally Wittliff, 1988 and ongoing
Biographical Note
Bill Wittliff was born in Taft, a small town in south Texas, in 1940. After his parents divorced, he and his brother Jim moved with their mother to Gregory, Texas, where Mrs. Wittliff ran a small telephone office during World War II (these experiences provided the basis for "Raggedy Man," Wittliff's feature film). Later, when his mother remarried, the family moved to a ranch in Blanco, a rural community of 700 in the hill country of central Texas.
In 1964, shortly after graduating from the University of Texas, Wittliff, with his wife Sally, founded a book publishing company, The Encino Press, which specialized in regional material about Texas and the Southwest. To date, Encino has won over 100 awards for quality of design and content. The press operated out of a 19th-century Victorian house in Austin in which O. Henry once lived and wrote.
An accomplished photographer, Wittliff's photographs documenting the life of the Mexican vaquero (taken 1969-71) have been exhibited in numerous galleries and institutions throughout this country and in Mexico, including the National Cowboy Hall of Fame, the Palacio de Bellas Artes in Mexico City, and the Texas Capitol. In Japan, they represented the United States during its bicentennial year. After twenty years, the exhibit is still shown as a traveling display in the U. S. and Mexico under the auspices of the Institute of Texan Cultures.
At 29, Wittliff was elected to the Texas Institute of Letters. He served as president during 1974-78, and sat on the Executive Council until 1990. In 1993, he was elected Fellow of the the Institute. He is a member of the historic Texas Philosophical Society, the Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences; and he served for six years on the Executive Board of Trustees of Robert Redford's Sundance Institute.
In 1985, with the donation of their lifelong collection of original manuscripts and books, Bill and Sally founded the Southwestern Writers Collection at Southwest Texas State University. Since that time the collection has grown rapidly, supported by donors from all over the country. It features original manuscripts by J. Frank Dobie, John Graves, Larry McMurtry, Walter Prescott Webb, Bud Shrake, Larry L. King, Horton Foote, Preston Jones, Sam Shepard, Willie Nelson, and many others. It also includes paintings by numerous regional artists including William Lester, Tom Lea, John Groth, Jerry Bywaters, Kermit Oliver, Robert Wade. Expanding the scope of the current facility, in 1996 the Wittliffs endowed the Wittliff Gallery of Southwestern and Mexican Photography which already includes works by Russell Lee, Manuel Alvarez Bravo, Ansel Adams, Keith Carter, Henri Cartier Bresson, Lola Bravo, Laura Gilpin, Edward Weston, Graciela Iturbide, Edward Curtis, Nacho Lopez, Erwin E. Smith, Marco Antonio Cruz, Jim Bones, Paul Strand, Mariana Yampolsky, and many others. Both collections are housed in eight specially designed rooms and a large, chambered gallery on the top floor of the Albert B. Alkek Library on the university campus.
Scope and Contents
The Bill Wittliff papers document the book publishing, photography, and screenwriting and filmmaking aspects of Mr. Wittliff's various professional and personal pursuits, ranging in date from 1968-1995, and including the following formats: correspondence, typescript drafts, bibliographies, woodcut blocks, illustrations, photographs, screenplay drafts, film storyboards and other production materials. See series descriptions within the container list for more detailed information.
Feature films; Screenplays; Screenwriters -- United States; Film; Motion pictures -- Production and direction; Photographers -- Texas; Publishers and publishing -- Texas; Authors; Motion picture industry; Literature; Photography; William D. Wittliff; William D. Wittliff; Encino Press
- Publishing, 1968-1975
  - Encino Press, 1968-1975
    Sub-Series Description
    The Encino Press file contains posters designed by Bill Wittliff and printed by Encino Press. There are original illustrations by John Groth for John Graves' The Last Running. The manuscript for Larry L. King's That Terrible Night That Santa Got Lost In The Woods is included along with correspondence, editing and original pen and ink scratchboard drawings by the Pulitzer Prize winning cartoonist, Pat Oliphant. Also contains manuscripts submitted to Wittliff for publication and the manuscript and galleys of the 1989 Encino Press bibliography by Gould Whaley, Jr. entitled William D. Wittliff and the Encino Press.
    - Posters and illustrations, 1968-1975 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - That Terrible Night, Larry L. King, 1980-1981 (Box 268, Folder 2-3)
    - That Terrible Night, Pat Oliphant illustrations, circa 1980 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Mss. submitted to Encino Press, not printed, 1966-1981 (Box 268, Folder 5-7)
    - Encino Press Bibliography, mss. and galley, 1989 (Box 268, Folder 8-9)
    - Encino Press Bibliography, galley, 1989 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Whitehead Encino Press Woodcuts, undated
    Original carved and inked woodblocks created by Barbara Whitehead commissioned by the Encino Press. These blocks have been scanned and printed on plain paper for ease of access. See print-outs and accompanying zip-disks in box 877. Print-outs are annotated with either a title taken from the block or simply a descriptive cataloger-assigned title; these are the titles listed in this quide. Prnt-outs are also annotated with the titles of books in which the images appeared, such as: Deep Like the Rivers (1969), Many Texans (1969), Living Texas (1969), Texas Folk Medicine (1970), Growing Up in Texas (1972), Texas Wild Game Cookbook (1972), and Peter Arbiter (1973).
    - Stephen F. Austin, pistol, rifle (Box 849)
    - Buffalo, canon, mug, church, LaSalle (Box 849)
    - Comet, Sky and children (Box 850)
    - Circus (Box 850)
    - Kids and Owl (Box 851)
    - Verso of Owl: woman seated on porch (Box 851)
    - Sewing / dancers (Box 851)
    - Boys (Box 852)
    - Covers (human figure under bed covers) (Box 852)
    - Telegraph and Texas (grandfather clock, rifle, state capitol, corn (Box 853)
    - Conquista, etc. (lady looking, pick axe, soldier, priest, house, Christmas tree, leaning man, sign "Goyen's Hill") (Box 853)
    - Hotel, Bronc (Box 854)
    - Sam Houston (Box 854)
    - Lady with crosses, corn plants, flag "Liberty or Death", tri-color flag, Indian and church, old machine (Box 855)
    - Barbed wire, bull, covered wagon, Stephen F. Austin, man with cane (Box 855)
    - Tomahawk, shape of Texas, Sam Houston, ear, 3 men and donkey, bowl, man (Box 856)
    - Men and boy (Box 856)
    - King, train (Box 857)
    - Bronc, stagecoach (Box 857)
    - Venison/deer, bird man (Box 858)
    - Pig and birds (Box 858)
    - Sodas, fire (Box 858)
    - Oil rig (Box 859)
    - Boy and car (Box 859)
    - Blender, spoons, garlic, corn, pot, bicycle (Box 860)
    - Nude figures (Box 860)
    - Boy flying (Box 861)
    - Figures running figures sitting on couch (Box 861)
    - Four men (2 seated, 2 standing) (Box 862)
    - Man playing fiddle (Box 862)
    - Cowboy (Box 862)
    - Three people [pioneers] (Box 862)
    - Boy in library reading (Box 863)
    - Satellite / spaceship (Box 863)
    - Windy sky view (Box 863)
    - Woman in a field (Box 863)
    - Horse, beetle, nude woman (Box 864)
    - Snake and cactus (Box 864)
    - Healing man w/ patient (Box 864)
    - Okra (Box 865)
    - Mouse and cowboy boot (Box 865)
    - Tombstone (Box 865)
    - Girls with calf (Box 865)
    - House (Box 866)
    - House and gate (Box 866)
    - House and trees (Box 867)
    - Quilt and trees (Box 867)
    - Ovals, man & rifle (Box 868)
    - Mermaid (Box 868)
    - Blender, squirrel, turkey, javelina, possum (Box 869)
    - Quail, big horn ram (Box 870)
    - Woman watering plants (Box 870)
    - Quail (Box 871)
    - Cowboy (Box 871)
    - Frog, lamb, chihuahua, scorpion, rabbit (Box 871)
    - Two women in oval w/ text "Deep Like the Rivers" (Box 872)
    - Houses, book (Box 872)
    - Armadillo (Box 872)
    - Woman, boy on tricycle in front of front (Box 872)
    - Jackrabbits and hunters (Box 873)
    - Woman's dress (Box 873)
    - Oil rig (Box 873)
    - Onion, bee, pig, cow, roadrunner, chicken (Box 874)
    - Gun, bones, cabin, man on horse, four men in oval with text "Texans" (Box 874)
    - Deer, star emblem, sword, canon/flag/lady, cabin, fort (Box 874)
    - Covered wagon, initials "FP" (Box 874)
    - Text "Encino Press books" (Box 875)
    - Text "At Christ…" with angel (Box 875)
    - J. Frank Dobie (Box 876)
    - Charles Goodnight (Box 876)
    - Train (Box 876)
    - Man on horse (Box 876)
    - Animals, Birds (Box 876)
    - Zip disks of woodblock images, print-outs of scanned woodblock images, in box number order, with bibliographic references on backs of print-outs (Box 877)
  - Writers/Artists, 1962-1989
    Manuscripts, articles, clippings, letters, prints, broadsides, and drawings of Southwestern writers and artists collected by Wittliff. Includes Steve Barthelme, Thomas Hart Benton, Joe Frantz, John Graves, Carl Hertzog, Bud Shrake, Bob Wade, and Walter Prescott Webb.
    - A - H (Box 269, Folder 2-8)
      Contents
      Glen Alyn; Steve Barthelme; Thomas Hart Benton; Bill Broyles; Jack Canson; Carlos W. Castaneda; Madison Cooper; J. Frank Dobie; Robert Duval; Steve Forbis; Joe Frantz; Larry Goodwyn; John Graves; Jim Hamm; Carl Hertzog; Tony Hillerman
    - K - Z (Box 270, Folder 1-5)
      Larry L. King; Tom Lea; David Lindsey; John A. Lomax; Al Lowman; Beverly Lowry; James McMurtry; Willie Nelson; Ancel Nunn; George Sessions Perry; Ellen Schulz Quillen; Bud Shrake; Henderson R. Shuffler; Terry Southern; Texas Hatters; Charles Phillip Vaughn; Bob Wade; Frank Wardlaw; Walter Prescott Webb
  - Texas Institute of Letters, 1957-1987
    The Texas Institute of Letters was organized in 1936 during the year of the Texas Centennial for the purpose of the "promotion and recognition of literature in Texas." It evolved into an organization which met annually and awarded literary prizes to works by Texas authors. Bill Wittliff joined the TIL in 1969 and was president from 1974 to 1978. He wrote and published a history of the Institute, The Texas Institute of Letters, 1936 - 1966. He and Encino Press had received awards from TIL beginning with his book design for an SMU Press printing of a lecture by Harry S. Truman. Wittliff designed and printed many TIL programs. Clippings about TIL are also found here along with the first copy of Texas Monthly signed by authors who were at the 1973 TIL meeting, and a cassette of the 1977 TIL meeting.
    - Programs, 1957-1979 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Programs, 1980-1987 (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Memorabilia, 1973 (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Anniversary meeting audiocassettes, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - Catalogs, Flyers, Programs, Pamphlets, Magazines, 1940-1992
    This sub-series contains Wittliff's collection of book catalogs, exhibition catalogs, printing pamphlets and historical society brochures. Invitations to readings, art and literature shows, directories, flyers, articles, clippings and notices are also present.
    - Book Catalogs, 1960-1973 (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Galleries, Special Collections, 1960-1973 (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - Book Presses and Dealers, 1988-1992 (Box 271, Folder 6-7)
    - Printing and graphics pamphlets, undated (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Graphics pamphlets, undated (Box 272, Folder 1-3)
    - Invitations, 1970-1983 (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Historical Societies, 1966-1973 (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Societies and Clubs, 1964-1992 (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Southwestern Writers Collection Dedication Program, signed, October 5, 1991 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Texana articles, newsletters, clippings, 1964-1992 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Magazines
      - Austin Weekly, January 1990 (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Austin Comic News, November, 1992 (Box 273, Folder 3-4)
      - Eros on Trial, 1966 (Box 273, Folder 5)
- Photography, 1969-1994
  Series Description
  In 1996, Bill and Sally Wittliff established the Wittliff Gallery - now the Southwestern & Mexican Photography Collection, and his photography was transferred to that collection
- Screenwriting, 1973-1995
  The Screenplays are arranged chronologically according to when they were written. The order does not reflect the order in which the films were released. The date following the title in parentheses is the release date. Photographs, film, and videotape may not be duplicated without permission from the Wittliff estate.
  - Barbarosa, 1973-1985
    A western starring Gary Busey and Willie Nelson. This series contains drafts of the script, costumes, photographs by Wittliff, the script supervisor's files, the editing and sound notes, publicity, distribution, and clippings of reviews and interviews. The archive also contains the dailies on film reels and a 16mm print of the film.
    - Scripts, 1973-1980
      - First draft, March 25 - April 8, 1973 (Box 274, Folder 1-2)
      - First draft revisions, undated (Box 274, Folder 3)
      - Second draft, undated (Box 274, Folder 4)
      - Rewrite, May 27, 1976-August 2, 1976 (Box 274, Folder 5-7)
      - Polish of rewrite, August 2, 1976 (Box 274, Folder 8-9)
      - Copy of polish, 1976 (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - Draft, October 18 - November 23, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 2-3)
      - Draft, November 24 - 29, 1979 (Box 275, Folder 4-7)
      - Schepisi's notes on November 19, 1979 draft, April 26, 1980 (Box 275, Folder 8)
      - Schepisi's notes on November 19, 1979 draft, April 26, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - Rewrite, pages 1-18, May 25, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - Rewrite, May 25 - June 24, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 3-6)
      - Second draft with Schepisi notes, June 24, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 7)
      - Second draft with Bud Shrake notes, June 24, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 8)
      - Second draft with Wittliff notes, June 24, 1980 (Box 276, Folder 9)
      - Third draft, August 3 - 13, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 1-4)
      - Fourth draft, August 28, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 5-6)
      - Polish of Aug 28, 1980 draft, September 11, 1980 (Box 277, Folder 7)
      - Shooting script, fourth draft with changes, undated (Box 277, Folder 8)
      - Fourth draft and notes, August 28, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 1-3)
    - Production, 1980-1985
      - Eric Williams script and notes, 1985 (Box 278, Folder 4)
      - Photographs by Wittliff, undated (Box 278, Folder 5)
      - Continuity Script, undated (Box 278, Folder 6)
      - Cutter's log, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 7)
      - Camera Reports, 1980 (Box 278, Folder 8-9)
      - Lab Reports, undated (Box 279, Folder 1)
      - Sound Reports, September-November, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 2)
      - Codebook, #1, #2, undated (Box 279, Folder 3-5)
      - Cutting and Sound, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 6)
      - ADR files, undated (Box 280, Folder 1-3)
      - Publicity and Distribution, 1981-1982 (Box 280, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, reviews, letters, 1981-1982 (Box 280, Folder 5-6)
  - Gally Hobbs (unproduced), 1973
    "My second attempt at writing a script--but it turned out to be only a collection of episodes based on my father's funeral and some of my high school experiences. So I shelved it after one draft." Bill Wittliff, December 22, 1988
    - First draft, September to October 11, 1973 (Box 281, Folder 1-5)
  - Thaddeus Rose and Eddie, 1973-1978
    Thaddeus Rose and Eddie was the first script written by Wittliff to be produced. The working title was "Sledge and Eddie," and some of the early drafts are titled as such. Wittliff's agent brought the script to the attention of producers Rod Sheldon and Dan Paulson. The TV movie was directed by Texas director Jack Starrett and starred Bo Hopkins and Johnny Cash. The film aired on the CBS network Friday Night Movies, February 24, 1978 to generally favorable reviews. The production brought Wittliff to the attention of producer/director Francis Ford Coppola who hired Wittliff to work on the script for The Black Stallion (1979). Wittliff credited the Coppola job for providing him validation as a screenwriter. This series contains drafts of the script, production forms, publicity and reviews. Also contains the drafts and galleys for the paperback Pinnacle Book based on the teleplay.
    - Scripts, 1973-1977
      - Rough draft & notes, October 18-November 2, 1973 (Box 281, Folder 6)
      - First draft, November 3, 1973 (Box 281, Folder 7-9)
      - Second draft, November 13-19, 1973 (Box 282, Folder 1)
      - Second draft, November 27, 1973 (Box 282, Folder 2-4)
      - Third draft, December 20, 1974-January 15, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 5-7)
      - Third draft polish, January 17, 1975 (Box 282, Folder 8)
      - Third draft polish, January 22-27, 1975 (Box 283, Folder 1)
      - Notes and fragments, January 23-27, 1975 (Box 283, Folder 2-3)
      - Rewrite for Paulson/CBS/Cash, undated (Box 283, Folder 4-5)
      - Revised first draft, September 19, 1977 (Box 283, Folder 6-7)
      - Revised draft, September 26, 1977 (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - Fragments and pages, undated (Box 284, Folder 2)
      - Revised draft, November 3, 1977 (Box 284, Folder 3)
      - Final revision, November 19, 1977 (Box 284, Folder 4-6)
    - Production, 1977-1978, undated
      - Production files (Cast and staff lists, shooting schedules and call sheets) (Box 284, Folder 7)
      - Congratulations (Box 284, Folder 8)
      - Reviews, 1977-1978 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Book adaptation by Sara Clark, Pinnacle Books, undated
      - Drafts (Box 285, Folder 2-5)
      - Galleys (Box 285, Folder 6)
      - Galleys (Box 286, Folder 1-2)
      - Cover pages & publicity (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Raggedy Man, 1973-1983
    A film loosely based on Wittliff's mother's life about a young, divorced mother of two sons working as a telephone operator in small-town Texas during World War II. Starring Sissy Spacek, Sam Shepard, and Eric Roberts. Early drafts are titled "Nita, Henry and Harry."
    - Scripts, 1973-1980
      - Rough draft of episodes, December 10, 1973 (Box 287, Folder 1-2)
      - First draft and rough draft, January 27, 1974 (Box 287, Folder 3)
      - First draft with corrections, January 27, 1974 (Box 287, Folder 4-5)
      - Rewrite for Noel Nasseck, September 16, 1975 (Box 287, Folder 6)
      - Rewrite, June 3-18, 1977 (Box 287, Folder 7)
      - Rewrite, June 3-18, 1977 (Box 288, Folder 1-2)
      - Scraps from LA trip & polish, June 19-23, 1977 (Box 288, Folder 3)
      - Second draft, June 29, 1977 (Box 288, Folder 4-5)
      - Partial rewrite for Universal, July 16, 1979 (Box 288, Folder 6)
      - Draft, August 22, 1979 (Box 288, Folder 7)
      - Draft, September 10, 1979 (Box 288, Folder 8)
      - Rewrite, September 13, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 1-3)
      - Polish, September 19-October 10, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 4)
      - Draft, October 10, 1979 (Box 289, Folder 5-6)
      - Changes, undated (Box 289, Folder 7)
      - Original typescript of partial draft, undated (Box 289, Folder 8)
      - Draft, April 16, 1980 (Box 289, Folder 9)
      - Draft, April 16, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 1)
      - Draft, April 17, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 2-7)
      - Changes made in Los Angeles, April 22 - 25, 1980 (Box 290, Folder 8)
      - Changes, undated (Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Second draft #188 & 144, April 30, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 2-3)
      - Wittliff script notes, memos, undated (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Production, 1980-1983
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 291, Folder 5)
      - Casting, April-June, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 6)
      - Location photos, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 7)
      - Shepard makeup, June 1980 (Box 291, Folder 8)
      - Shooting, One-line schedules, June - December, 1980 (Box 291, Folder 9)
      - Wittliff's production notebook, July 1980 (Box 291, Folder 10)
      - Wittliff's production notebook, July 1980 (Box 292, Folder 1)
      - Wittliff photographs, undated (Box 292, Folder 2)
      - Costume-pilot cap (Box 292, Folder 3)
      - Inserts, undated (Box 292, Folder 4)
      - Budget, Progress Reports, August-December, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 5)
      - Call Sheets, October 20 - December 17, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 6)
      - Daily Production Reports, October 13 - December 18, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 7)
      - Second Unit Dec, 1980 (Box 292, Folder 8)
      - Editing, Spotting List, undated (Box 292, Folder 9)
      - Distribution, 1983 (Box 292, Folder 10)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 292, Folder 11)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 293, Folder 1)
      - Congratulations, 1981-1983 (Box 293, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, 1980-1981 (Box 293, Folder 3-4)
    - Book Adaptation, 1979, undated
      - First Draft (Box 293, Folder 5)
      - Typescript, circa 1979 (Box 293, Folder 6)
      - Typescript with changes (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - Book revisions (Box 294, Folder 2)
      - First galley, February 24, 1979 (Box 294, Folder 3)
      - Promotion (Box 294, Folder 4)
      - Paperback (Box 294, Folder 5)
  - Night in Old Mexico (Tattoo), 1974-1988
    The film was eventually produced in 2013 starring Robert Duvall.
    - Scripts, 1974-1988, undated
      - Notes, undated (Box 295, Folder 1)
      - Rough draft of episodes, July 2, 1974 (Box 295, Folder 2)
      - First draft, August 4, 1974 (Box 295, Folder 3)
      - First draft, August 13, 1974 (Box 295, Folder 4-8)
      - Second draft, November 8, 1974 (Box 295, Folder 9)
      - Second draft, November 8, 1974 (Box 296, Folder 1)
      - Second draft revision, November 12, 1974 (Box 296, Folder 2)
      - Third draft, March 2, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 3-4)
      - Third draft polish, March 26, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 5-8)
      - First rewrite, July 1975 (Box 297, Folder 1-2)
      - Rewrite, July 30, 1975 (Box 297, Folder 3)
      - Tattoo Final polish, November 10-13, 1975 (Box 297, Folder 4-5)
      - Tattoo old copy used in Jun 1977 rewrite, undated (Box 297, Folder 6)
      - First rough draft, June 1, 1977 (Box 298, Folder 1-2)
      - Draft, March 13, 1979 (Box 298, Folder 3-5)
      - Draft, December 28, 1980 - January 26, 1981 (Box 298, Folder 6-7)
      - Polish begun, January 27, 1981 (Box 298, Folder 8)
      - First draft, February 25, 1981 (Box 299, Folder 1-4)
      - Rewrite begun, March 4 - 28, 1981 (Box 299, Folder 5)
      - Second draft, April 6 (Box 299, Folder 6-8)
      - Rewrite, June 17 - August 20, 1982 (Box 299, Folder 9)
      - Rewrite, June 17 - August 20, 1982 (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - Polish, August 21 - 26, 1982 (Box 300, Folder 2-4)
      - Rewrite, August 25 - October 16, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 5-6)
      - Polish begun, October 21, 1985 (Box 300, Folder 7-8)
      - Polish, October 21 - November 11, 1985 (Box 301, Folder 1-5)
      - Rewrite, September 30 - December 9, 1988 (Box 301, Folder 6-7)
      - Polish, December 12-18, 1988 (Box 302, Folder 1-3)
  - The Terrible Teague Bunch, 1975
    - by Gary Jennings (Box 303, Folder 1-4)